Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series B-MT, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series B. Inactive File, Pre 1980
  - Powell, Adam Clayton (Box B-7, Folder 2)
    Press release dated 7-5-1965, endorsing the Voting Rights Act (2 leaves); typescript postcard from the "Harlem Bi-Partisan Committee to Stop Powell" (1 leaf); copy of a typed letter from Powell to Omar Burleson (6 leaves); 1 blank sheet of Adam Powell Day Committee (In Formation) letterhead; mimeographed minutes of a meeting of the Adam Powell Day Committee, with cover letter by John H. Young (3 leaves total); typed letter signed by Herman P. Osborne and George A. Weston to James Hicks, dated 9-14-1964, concerning Adam Powell Day (1 leaf); typed note from "Odell" to "Jimmy" [Hicks?], undated (1 leaf); empty envelope addressed to James Hicks from the House of Representatives, postmarked 12-18-1963; empty envelope addressed to "Miss Wade" and James Hicks, from Consolidated Publishers, undated; typed letter signed by Herbert M. Gussack of Saga Magazine to the Amsterdam News, dated 6-25-1963, concerning an article on Powell in Saga (1 leaf); attachment note from an unidentified piece of correspondence, dated in ms. 3-6-1964; 7 leaves of ms. notes; 5 leaves of photocopied ms. notes; and approximately 110 original and 1 photocopied newspaper clippings.
  - Powell, Adam Clayton (Box B-7, Folder 3)
    Note on folder: "1967 Jan.-July." Approximately 188 newspaper clippings.
  - Powell, Adam Clayton (Box B-7, Folder 4)
    Note on original folder: "1967 Jan.-July." Newswire text concerning a vote to censure Powell, dated 3-2-1967 (1 leaf with attached ms. cover note); press release dated 2-23-1967 concerning a statement by the National Urban League in defense of Powell (1 leaf); mimeographed announcement of "Adam Powell Week" (Jan. 4-11, 1967) published by the United American Appeal (2 copies, each leaves); undated "Statement by Dr. Eugene S. Calendar" of the National Urban League in defense of Powell (1 leaf); handbill "Message from the Grass Roots: Calling for the Trial of All Congressmen who Oppose Powell" (2 copies, each 1 leaf); News Bulletin #119 of the Harlem Council for Economic Development, concerning funds for Powell's defense (4 leaves); mimeographed "Resolution" of the Pilgrimage to Preserve Powell's Chairmanship, The Ministers' and Laymen's Assembly (Jan. 8, 1967; 1 leaf, with ms. notes on verso); mimeographed "Open Letter to Ministers and Laymen" from the Pilgrimage to Preserve Powell's Chairmanship (Jan. 4, 1967) (2 copies, each 2 leaves); press release dated 1-8-1967 from the Pilgrimage to Preserve Powell's Chairmanship, with attached copy of the "Resolution" of the Pilgrimage bearing the same date (2 copies, each 3 leaves); program of the Ministers' and Layman's Assembly of the Pilgrimage to Preserve Powell's Chairmanship (1 leaf); press release dated 1-14-[1967] concerning a statement by Roy Wilkins in defense of Powell; autograph letter signed by H.H. Cain to the Amsterdam News, dated 3-18-1967; carbonscript letter signed by Gerald R. Ford to Harrison H. Cain, dated 3-15-1967 (1 leaf); 3 issues of newsletter "Your Washington Review" by Gerald R. Ford (dated Mar. 1, 8, and 15, 1967), with attached Jan/Feb. 1967 supplement and one newspaper clipping (5 leaves total); carbonscript letter from David N. Licorish to Mayor John V. Lindsay dated 1-7-1967 (2 leaves); carbonscript text by the National Committee for Black Power, including a "Tribute to Adam Clayton Powell" (2 leaves); press release dated 1-5-1967 containing a statement by Powell entitled "15 Facts" (4 leaves); typescript article draft "To Jews?" by Gaylord Axelrod, dated 1-14-1967 (3 leaves, plus attached cover leaf); press release dated 1-11-1967 concerning Howard K. Smith's comments on "The Powell Trouble" (2 leaves); press release dated 1-12-1967 concerning a CBS TV special on "Powell's Harlem" (2 leaves); mimeographed "Open Letter to Congressman John Conyers, Jr. of Detroit" by Revs. Walter A. Gray and Cleveland B. Sparrow, dated 2-13-1967 (4 leaves); 2nd leaf only of an unidentified press release on "The Powell Trouble"; final leaf only of a carbonscript "Statement by Mr. Young on Adam Clayton Powell"; 1 leaf of ms. notes, and 7 newspaper clippings.
  - Powell, Adam Clayton (Birth certificate) (Box B-7, Folder 5)
    Photocopy of Powell's birth certificate, with ms. notations.
  - Powell, Adam Clayton - FoundationInc. (Box B-7, Folder 6)
    Press release dated Apr. 7 [no year], on Powell Foundation grant for Crossroads Africa (3 leaves) and 2 newspaper clippings.
  - Powell, Adam Clayton (Box B-7, Folder 7)
    Note on folder: "People's Voice, 1944-1945." Carbonscript press release dated 4-10-1944, concerning a statement issued by Congressman Vito Mar Antonio, responding to claims by Buckley and Maron (1 leaf); undated press release concerning Powell's endorsement of Richard Frankenstein for mayor of Detroit (2 leaves); press release dated 2-24-45 concerning Rep. John Rankin's insinuation that Rep. Frank Hook and Powell had communist ties (2 leaves); undated press release on Powell's endorsement of Bill O'Dwyer for Mayor of New York (2 leaves); carbonscript press release dated 5-26-1947, signed by Harrison S. Jackson, concerning Powell's inability to spearhead the Negro Freedom Rally due to illness (1 leaf, plus cover sheet); broadside reprinting several newspaper articles ca. 4-6-1946 regarding the murder of two soldiers, issued by Veterans Justice Committee (1 leaf); empty envelope address in ms. to the Amsterdam News; and approximately 45 newspaper clippings.
  - Powell, Adam Clayton, Sr. (FundInc.) (Box B-7, Folder 8)
    Fragments of two autograph letters, one dated 7-6-1950, on AC Powell Sr. Fund letterhead, and a brochure for the Vocational Guidance Center.
  - Powell, Adam Clayton, III (Box B-7, Folder 9)
    4 newspaper clippings.
  - Powell Committee Bar & Theater Investigation (Box B-7, Folder 10)
    37 copied leaves of hearing transcripts in three sections, each with a single typescript cover leaf.
  - Powell, Bud (Box B-7, Folder 11)
    2 prints have staples through border.
    Photographer if identified: Carole Galletly, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Air France Photo
  - Powell, C.B. (Box B-7, Folder 12)
    Note on folder: "See: Inactive file (also gray boxes on top of cabinet)."
  - Prattis, P.L. (Box B-7, Folder 13)
    Also mimeographed "Address by Robert C. Weaver... P. L. Prattis Testimonial Dinner... Oct. 20, 1961."
  - Presley, Elvis (Box B-7, Folder 14)
  - Procope, Russell (Box B-7, Folder 15)
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, James Gilbert, Hans Harzheim
  - Randolph, A. Philip (Box B-7, Folder 16)
    Pamphlet "A. Philip Randolph at 80: Tributes and Recollections," containing excerpts from speeches made at Randolph's 80th birthday dinner, May 6, 1969, with 5 inserted handbills and photocopies; pamphlet "Annual Report of the A. Philip Randolph Institute: November 1968-November 1969" (2 copies); printed fundraising letter by Bayard Rustin dated Feb. 1970 (1 leaf); mimeographed "Statement by A. Philip Randolph" dated 9-10-1968, endorsing Hubert Humphrey (4 leaves, with attached mailing envelope and single-leaf press release of the same date); printed packet from the "A. Philip Randolph Society Luncheon honoring A. Philip Randolph... and Installation of Officers", 6-24-1972 (5 leaves); pamphlet "The Anatomy of Frustration: An Address by Bayard Rustin" (delivered at the 55th National Commission Meeting of the Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith, 5-6-1968); mass-mailed letter by Bayard Rustin dated July 1968, with offprinted articles "Education in a Changing Society" and "The Labor-Negro Coalition - A New Beginning," both by Rustin; mass-mailed letter by Rustin dated 1-16-1968, with 2 attached leaves of photocopied newspaper articles, one mimeographed letter from Vernon E. Jordan to the New York Times dated 1-5-1968, and the complete Nov. 1967 issue of The Federationist; mimeographed letter from Willie Baxter to George Meany dated 10-1-1959 (2 leaves); Randolph Institute memorandum dated Apr. 1967 (3 leaves); typescript text "Summer and Smoke" by Rustin, with attached typed cover letter signed by Rustin dated 4-27-1967 (5 leaves total); memorandum dated 5-16-1967 by Rustin, with attached newsletter Youth Action on the Freedom Budget (4-30-1967 issue); pamphlet "'Right to Work' Laws--A Trap for America's Minorities" by Rustin, with attached mass-mailing cover letter dated May 1967; and 19 newspaper clippings.
  - Randolph, A. Philip (Box B-7, Folder 17)
    Mimeographed letter from the Salute to A. Philip Randolph Committee (Harry Emerson Fosdick, Martin Luther King Jr., and Roy Wilkins) announcing a 70th birthday celebration for Randolph at Carnegie Hall on 1-24-1960 (1 leaf, with attached mailing envelope); pamphlet "The A. Philip Randolph Story" (dated 1974 in ms.); press release, undated, announcing Randolph's 87th birthday celebration on 4-17-[1975] (1 leaf, with attached biography, 6 leaves); mimeographed "Biographical Sketch" (1 leaf); press release (undated, ca. Oct. 1974) announcing a sculptural tribute to Randolph (2 leaves); press release dated 5-18-1979 announcing Randolph's death (2 leaves); press release dated 11-4-1974 concerning Randolph's receipt of the Dept. of Labor's Award of Merit (1 leaf); 2 leaves of typescript quotations in memory of Randolph; booklet A 'Freedom Budget' For All Americans (Oct. 1966); program from a memorial service for Randolph held 6-19-1979 at Lincoln Center, with attached "Biographical Notes"; memorial pamphlet "Asa Philip Randolph: In Memoriam, April 15, 1889 to May 16, 1979"; and 4 newspaper clippings.
  - Randolph, A. Philip (Box B-7, Folder 18)
    Also a mass-mailed cover letter dated Jun./Jul. 1971 (1 leaf), with two enclosures: pamphlet The Blacks and the Unions by Bayard Rustin and flier advertising the pamphlet "The Neglected Black Minority"; mimeographed memorandum by Bayard Rustin dated 5-22-1971, addressed in ms. to "Jesse" (1 leaf, with 3-leaf "Statement on the Minimum Wage"); and pamphlet "A. Philip Randolph: Labor's Grand Old Man" by Phyl Garland.
    Photographer if identified: Bill Carter, James Gilbert, L. St. Clair Dummett
  - Randolph, A. Philip (Box B-7, Folder 19)
    Also two velox prints and one typescript article text.
    Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Alvin J. Burley, Bill Carter, A. Hansen Studio, Gaffney Photo, Curt Clemons, King Photographers, Calr Nesfield, Alexander Archer, Wenger & Petrucci Inc.,
  - Ray, Sandy F. (The Rev. Dr.) (Box B-7, Folder 20)
    Also one negative, one typed letter signed by Daniel P. Barr to Jim Booker dated 2-24-1966 (1 leaf); two velox prints, and one image removed from an unidentified publication.
    Photographer if identified: EnellInc., The Allen Studio, Ace Creative Photos, Rufus Merritt, The Bing Studio, Monclova Photographers, King Photographers, Harris Photo, W. Smith, Gill Photographers, Herbert Hawkins, Tex Harris, Alex Summers Photos
  - Razaf, Andy (Box B-7, Folder 21)
    With attached photocopied notice of Razaf's illness, dated 12-19-1972 (3 leaves), with 3 leaves of additional photocopied material.
  - Reid, Ferdinand T. (Box B-7, Folder 22)
    Program from Reid's funeral, held 12-31-1973 at Saint Philip's Church.
  - Richardson, Scovel (Judge) (Box B-7, Folder 23)
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise
  - Richardson, Maude B. (Box B-7, Folder 24)
    One print has two staples through the border; one has a staple through the corner of the image.
    Photographer if identified: King Photographers, Dave Greene/Creative Photo Service Inc., Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Alex Hamilton, Monclova Photographers, Herbert Hawkins, James Gilbert
  - Rieves (Funeral) (Box B-7, Folder 25)
    Approximately 9 prints stuck together in a bundle with paste.
  - Riperton, Minnei (Box B-7, Folder 26)
    Photographer if identified: American Cancer Society Picture File
  - Rivers, Francis E. (Justice) (Box B-7, Folder 27)
    Pamphlet "Proposal for a Federal Civil Rights Procedure Act... March 1966," with enclosed 2-leaf photocopied press release and two newspaper clippings; press release dated 6-17-1957 concerning Rivers' election to leader of American Legion post 843, with ms. annotation (2 leaves); carbonscript biographical data (3 leaves); typescript editorial advocating the appointment of Rivers to the Federal District Court, with ms. corrections (2 leaves); ms. text "To Protect the Exercise of These Rights!" (7 leaves); typescript editorial text advocating the appointment of Rivers to the Federal District Court (3 leaves); and mixed ms. and typescript text "The Color Line in the Federal Courts" (9 ms. and 3 typescript leaves with ms. corrections; 12 leaves total).
  - Rivers, Francis E. (Justice) (Box B-7, Folder 28)
    One print has a two-leaf press release attached with a paperclip. Also two negatives, one velox print, and one paper stereotype matrix.
    Photographer if identified: Cecil Layne, Layne's Studio, Wert Hooper, Dummett, Loris Boone, U.S. Army, Haywood Carter, Carrington, Smith, Liberty Flashlight Co., Blencle [sp?], North Carolina College News Bureau, Dummet/Rapid News Photo
  - Robeson, Paul (Box B-7, Folder 29)
    Photographer if identified: United Press International Inc., Smith, International News Photos, Nichols, Grant, James C. Campbell, Gene Dauber, Dave Greene Photo, Bennett College Publicity Office, Llewellyn Ransom, Lucas & Monroe Studio, Vandamm Studio, Mr. Ramirez
  - Robeson, Paul (Box B-7, Folder 30)
    Also two negatives (4 images); photocopy of a letter from Paul Robeson to "Friends," dated 4-9-1973 (1 leaf); prospectus flier for 16mm release of The Emperor Jones (1 leaf); 10 paper stereotype matrices, and approximately 28 velox prints (many stuck together with wax paste).
    Photographer if identified: Ed McPherson, Pictorial Enterprise, International News Photos, Nichols, Fay Foto Service Inc., A. Hansen, Dummett, James C. Campbell, Keystone Pictures Inc.
  - Robeson, Paul (Box B-8, Folder 1)
    Also program from Robeson's funeral (held Jan. 27, 1976 at Mother A.M.E. Zion Church); a 14-leaf text edited from pasted-on photocopies and original pages from books by Robeson and typescript passages, with ms. corrections; 2 velox prints; and 34 newspaper clippings. Two prints are stuck together with paste.
    Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, United Press International Inc., International News Photos, Capitol, R. Smith/Rapid News Photo, Signal Corps
  - Robeson, Paul (Box B-8, Folder 2)
    Photocopy of a letter by James Earl Jones to unidentified recipient dated 6-22-1977 (2 leaves); packet of 4 photocopied letters between Martin Popper, Paul Robeson Jr, and officials at NBC, dated from 2-3-1976 to 3-4-1976 concerning an NBC special on the life of Robeson (4 leaves); packet of photocopied correspondence between Charles Rangel and Paul Robeson Jr., dated from 11-30-1977 to 2-13-1978 (5 leaves); packet of transcripts from NBC dated between 2-9-1978 and 3-2-1978, concerning James Earl Jones's play about Robeson (13 leaves); photocopied letter by the National Ad Hoc Committee to End the Crimes Against Paul Robeson to WNBC-TV dated 2-27-1978 (6 leaves); printed biographical cartoon by Alston (1 leaf); photocopy of text "A Man Before His Time: A Tribute" by Dr. Nathan Wright (1 leaf); typed letter signed by Chris Reynolds to Lucia Robinson dated 4-1-1977 (1 leaf, with 2 attached two-leaf press releases); press release dated 2-24-1978 containing an address given by Tran Van Dinh on that date entitled "Here We All Stand" (4 leaves), with two attached newspaper clippings; photocopied "Address by Mayor Richard Hatcher: Salute to Paul Robeson" dated 4-15-1973 (6 leaves); typescript leaf containing memorial quotes about Robeson from Georgia Jenkins and Adelle Lambert; carbonscript text "My Meetings with Paul Robeson" by Konstantin Kudrov (5 leaves); mimeographed legal complaint Paul Robeson v. Dean G. Acheson (U.S. District Court for the District of Columbia, Civil Action no. 5500-50) (17 leaves); photocopied "Tribute by Bishop J. Clinton Hoggard" dated 1-27-1976 (4 leaves); press release dated 4-26-1945 concerning Robeson's receipt of the Spingarn Medal; souvenir program from the Spingarn Medal ceremony on Oct. 18, 1945carbonscript text "Ten Thousand Welcome Robeson at Wrigley Field..." by Rev. Daniel L. Reed (3 leaves); press release dated 8-9-1950 concerning the voiding of Robeson's passport by the State Department; press release dated 10-24-1950 containing the text of a speech delivered by Robeson at the American Labor Union Party Rally on that date; typed letter signed by Victor Grossman to the Amsterdam News concerning the founding of a Robeson Archive at the German Academy of Arts; and one photocopied newspaper clipping.
  - Robinson, Bill (Box B-8, Folder 3)
    6 newspaper clippings.
  - Robinson, Jackie (Box B-8, Folder 4)
    Also offset-printed text "When the 'Booker T. Washington' Took to the Air" by Allen Keller. Folder includes several items related to Booker T. Washington (possibly mis-filed).
    Photographer if identified: Wagner International Photos, Mario Cabrera, Harris Photo, C. Gerald Fraser, Sanchez Y Cabredo, Herbert Hawkins, Peterkin Photo
  - Robinson, Jackie (Funeral) (Box B-8, Folder 5)
    Two prints stuck together with paste.
  - Robinson, James H (Rev.) (Box B-8, Folder 6)
    One print has a 2-leaf press release attached with a paperclip.
    Photographer if identified: Scurlock, Harris Photo, Paul Begley, David McAdams, A. Hansen Studio, Guy Gillette, TWA, Paul Cordes, James Gilbert, Gin Briggs
  - Robinson, Sugar Ray (Box B-8, Folder 7)
    Three prints are mounted on paperboard. One print has caption attached with staple through corner of image. One print has typed letter signed by Syd Rubin to "Mr. Walker" attached with a paperclip.
    Photographer if identified: Paul Popper Ltd., Wide World Photos, United Press International Inc., James J. Kriegsmann, James Gilbert, Paul Schumach/Metropolitan Photo Service Inc., Katrina Thomas, Bro. David McAdams, Wagner International Photos
  - Rochester, "Eddie" (Box B-8, Folder 8)
  - Rodney, Walter Anthony (Box B-8, Folder 9)
    One image removed from the pamphlet "Walter Rodney: Revolutionary and Scholar: A Tribute."
  - Rodwell, Ronald (Box B-8, Folder 10)
    Program from funeral service (Aug. 12, 1976 at Farley's Funeral Parlors).
  - Rojas, Ron (Box B-8, Folder 11)
    Photographer if identified: Peterkin Photo, Portfolio International Photographers
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor (Box B-8, Folder 12)
    "Information Kit" from the Eleanor Roosevelt Memorial Foundation (folder containing 3 brochures, 2 packets, and 3 individual pages, ca. 23 leaves total); mimeographed text "First Lady Answers Alabama White Woman" (1 leaf); undated press release concerning accusations against Roosevelt by Charles W. Anderson Jr. (2 leaves); undated press release on a speech delivered by Roosevelt in support of Adlai Stevenson (3 leaves); 3 pamphlets: Amendments 51, 52, and 53 to the "Rent and Eviction Regulations" of N.Y. State (12 p. total); packet of press materials relating to the Eleanor Roosevelt Memorial Foundation (10 leaves, one invitation, one brochure, and 2 newspaper clippings); "Memo to Editors" dated 10-9-1963 from the Eleanor Roosevelt Memorial Foundation; invitation to an International Tribute to Eleanor Roosevelt (held 10-21-1963) signed by Eli Jaffe, with printed invitation and single-leaf press release attached; and 65 newspaper clippings.
  - Rose, Peyton (Box B-8, Folder 13)
  - Rowe, Billy (Box B-8, Folder 14)
    Approximately 58 newspaper clippings.
  - Rustin, Bayard (Box B-8, Folder 15)
    Also press release obituary (4 leaves), 11 newspaper clippings, and 5 velox prints (3 pasted up on a single leaf of paper).
    Photographer if identified: Bro. David McAdams, Irene B. Bayer, L. St. Clair Dummett, Harris Photo, Herbert Bennett, J. Bernard, News Voice International, Burke & Dean, University of Hartford News Bureau, Cooper
  - Ruth, George Herman "Babe" (Box B-8, Folder 16)
  - Sadat, Anwar (President) (Box B-8, Folder 17)
    One computer-printed drawing of Sadat.
  - Samuel, Fred (Box B-8, Folder 18)
    Note on folder: "Also see Harlem Assertion of Rgts." Also legal complaint "Thomas Davis V. Maurice H. Stans... George H. Brown... and John C. Cullinane" (U.S. District Court for the Southern District of New York) (19 leaves); "Vote for Fred Samuel" handbill; campaign brochure "Fred's the One for 'A Better Harlem'" (1970); press release dated 2-10-1970 concerning the formation of a Testimonial Committee for Samuel (2 leaves); mimeographed Memorandum from Howard Samuels to Gov. Nelson Rockefeller (ca. 1970, 1 leaf); press release dated 9-12-1985 concerning a tribute to Samuel, with one attached typescript leaf.
  - Sands, Diana (Box B-8, Folder 19)
    Also one typed letter signed by Lawrence N. Belling (1 leaf) and one newspaper clipping. One print is a Polaroid. One print has a staple through the border; one print has a staple through the corner of the image.
    Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Robert Fuhring, Friedman-Abeles, Jerry Baron, Mallory, The Bayside Studio, Bill Carter, Paul Schumach, Wagner International Photo, Al Burley, Green-Morris Studios, George West, Hamilton Associates, Lloyd Yearwood, Bert Andrews, Tommy Sands
    Number of Prints: 46
  - Sankara, Thomas (Box B-8, Folder 20)
  - Savory, Philip Maxwell Hugh (Dr.) (Box B-8, Folder 21)
    One postcard and one information card from the Madison Avenue Baptist Church; two carbonscript copies of an obituary press release (5 leaves total); two photocopied copies of an obituary press release (6 leaves); and one typescript note.
    Photographer if identified: A. Hansen
  - Savory, Philip Maxwell Hugh (Dr.) (Box B-8, Folder 22)
    One photo has handbill from a protest against the Amsterdam News (for refusing an ad urging a boycott of Lever Bros. products) attached with a paperclip. Two prints are mounted on paperboard. Also one velox print.
    Photographer if identified: A. Hansen, Nichols, Richardson's Photos, W. Smith, Keno Foto Service, Dummett, Rapid News Photo, James Gilbert, James C. Campbell, Samuel Johnson, Lillian Wright, W. Smith/Rapid News Photo, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, M&M Smith, Cecil Layne
  - Savory, Philip Maxwell Hugh (Dr.) (Box B-8, Folder 23)
    Also 30 negatives (45 images total), carbonscript letter from C.B. Powell to Gladys E. Savory dated 7-1-1965 (1 leaf), complete Jun. 19, 1965 issue of the Amsterdam News with a front-page story on Savory's death, one envelope containing approximately 7 small images of Savory removed from newspapers.
    Photographer if identified: British Overseas Airways Corp (BOAC), Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Bro. David McAdams, James C. Campbell, G.G. Photo Studio, Dummett, Lillian Wright
  - Savory, Philip Maxwell Hugh (Dr.) (Death) (Box B-8, Folder 24)
    Front page only of the Jun. 19, 1965 issue of the Amsterdam News with a front-page story on Savory's death, and carbonscript intra-office "Notice" by C. B. Powell dated Jun. 11, 1965 announcing Savory's death.
  - Sayles, Kiah (Box B-8, Folder 25)
    Also 3 velox prints.
    Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Bob Mabley
  - Schiffman, Frank (Box B-8, Folder 26)
  - Schuyler, George S. (Box B-8, Folder 27)